VÕ THỊ NGỌC TRẦM



Summary -

For 4 years at the university, I learned basic science subjects, the operational principles and practice of electronic sensors and semiconductor devices, optics, calculation methods, and also increase logical thinking and creative. I hope that the knowledge learned will meet the recruitment needs of the company. I am confident that if given the opportunity, I can be a useful member of the company.



Education -

VIET NAM NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

2014 - 2018

- HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF SIENCE

Major: Applied Physics

GPA: 7.3



Certifications

- Certificate of English 4 skills Vietnam International University 188.
- "The 14th School on Micro-Nanotechnology" MINATEC 2017

Knowledge

Modules included:

- Fundamentals of Semiconductor Device (Diode, Transistor, LED,...)
- Optics, Sensor and measurement, Basic electronics
- Basis Computational Mathematics (MATLAB)
- Materials Analysis Techniques
- Spectroscopy
- Fundamentals of Nano Properties and Nano Technologies



Experience

EXPERIENCE IN PHYSICS LABORATORY

AUG 2017 - JUL 2018

Research 1 year in laboratory at university of sience.

- Ability to use UV-Vis spectrophotometry to obtain UV-Vis spectra of samples.
- Knowing how to set up PL system to measure PL spectra for QDs.
- Learning how to use Laser, Laser beam profiler.
- How to operate the sputtering machine, thin films production.

SHOPEE COMPANY

MAY 2017 - DEC 2017

Collaborators

-Check price of product



- **30/09/1996**
- Female
- 01644122825
- ngoctram300996@gmail.com
- Ninh Thuan / Viet Nam
- i Ngọc Trầm

SKILLS -

Office

Willingness to listen to and learn new things

Organized

Problem solving

Team work

Communication

Creativity

English

INTERESTS

• Swimming, music, read book, creativity,...